♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Ah, Smitty's Steakhouse.
You know, this was the
fanciest restaurant in Quahog
when I was a kid.
The ladies' room has a big space
with chairs in it, like a living
room, before you get back
to where the crappers are.
Good evening and
welcome to Smitty's.
I'll be back with
martinis for Mom and Dad,
and for you kids,
some martinis.
Dad, can you pass
the bread?
Sure. But don't forget
the butter that looks like
decorative bathroom soaps and
is impossible to smear.
Thanks, Dad!
This really ruins it!
What will you
be having, sir?
Yes, I'll have what I had last
time: pheasant on the glass.
Don't you mean
"pheasant under glass"?
Nope.
Yeah. Now turn around
and lay an egg on the glass.
Aw, yeah.
I defy you to tell me
exactly what's wrong with this.
Oh, Peter, look.
You can put your business card
in this bowl
and maybe win a free lunch.
I don't have a
business card.
And I think
you knew that.
I hope you enjoyed
your meal, sir.
May I offer you a toothpick?
Oh, I-I don't know.
We've already spent
a lot of money in here tonight.
No, sir, it-it's free.
Oh!
Peter, that's not how
you use a toothpick.
You pick your teeth
with it.
I cannot believe I have
to explain this to you.
There are gaps in my knowledge.
This is hardly news.
Wow, this is awesome!
This is like
I'm having a whole second meal!
Man, this just feels right.
That's it. From here on out, I
am about all things toothpick.
I'm gonna go everywhere with
it, always be chewin' on it,
#-and start all my
sentences with,
"All right, here's
what you're gonna do."
Excuse me, we're
from out of town.
Where do people go to listen
to live music around here?
I'll handle this. All right,
here's what you're gonna do:
skip the live music.
Get yourself a room
over at the Wickford Marina.
Take her out on a balcony,
point to any boat in the harbor,
and tell her it's yours.
Now, you got rubbers?
Now that I'm a toothpick guy,
I call 'em rubbers. Or you could
just pull the hose out
of the bucket
and let it spray free.
I've had a vasectomy.
Chris, now that I'm a toothpick
guy, it's my job to sit
on a BMX bike
outside the rec center
and ask every kid
if they're the new kid.
Hey. You the new kid?
Why?
Never mind why.
Got any cool toys?
Uh, I got an Xbox.
How about you?
I got a Barbie with a wiener on it.
Took a thumb from a G.I. Joe,
put it on with superglue.
Looks pretty real.
Real enough, anyways.
Does the job.
Does what job?
You get it. My family
moves around a lot
'cause I do stuff like this.
Um... okay.
I got to go now.
You sure you don't want
to come over and pull
on my cat's nipples?
We can do anything,
'cause my mom has two jobs.
All right,
I'm off to the fish market.
What? Why?
Well, the most intimidating
people are toothpick guys
who work at seafood counters
and make people uncomfortable
for not knowing
about fish.
What's good here?
It's all good.
What's the freshest?
It's all fresh.
How 'bout the halibut?
Is it gamey?
Gamey?
I mean, you know, is it fishy?
It's all fish.
Is there a special way to prepare it?
I'd cook it up.
W-Well, what's
the best fish here?
What's your favorite fish?
I don't eat fish.
I only like spaghetti.
Ugh, when are you gonna
get rid of that toothpick?
It's disgusting,
and it's starting to smell.
Why would I give it up?
It's gettin' me tons of tail.
What?
And check this out.
The rare triple toothpick flip.
Oh, my God,
are you all right?
No, I swallowed it!
My toothpick! It's gone!
Damn it! I'm gonna need
you to put that large
two-handed colander
over the toilet.
Peter, that was
a wedding present from my aunt.
Well, let's use
the ice cream maker!
We've never used it once!
Calm down. You can always get
another toothpick.
Oh, my God, you're right!
Lois, we got to drive
to Smitty's right now
and get one.
Now? But we told Chris
we'd be there
when he wakes up from surgery.
All right, we were able
to fix your hernia,
but you've got to stop lifting
sewer hole covers.
But the Ninja Turtles
live down there.
I'm friends with them.
Hey, fat ass,
I brought you flowers.
But stay out of the sewers!
We're trying to work down there.
Thanks, Donatello!
Oh, thank God!
Quick, we need
another toothpick!
Thank you, Maurice.
Just get your toothpick
and let's get out of here.
Ugh. No, thanks.
That old lady has ruined
toothpicks for me.
Just like how Meg
ruined broccoli.
Hey, Meg, look,
they're little trees!
No, they're not.
They're not?!
Hey, Peter!
Oh, look, there's Quagmire
and his transgendered mother,
which is now great.
Hey, Quagmire. Hey, Ida.
I didn't know
you liked Smitty's.
Oh, yeah, I've been coming here
for ages.
They even named a sandwich
after me.
It's an inside-out hot dog
slathered in ketchup.
Please, please
join us.
Oh, we wouldn't want
to interrupt your brave dinner.
Nonsense, we're happy
to have you.
All right,
but we already ate dinner,
so maybe just an iceberg wedge,
a steak, and some sides.
And then I said something random
that suggested
a whole crazy story!
Oh, God, that's
hilarious, Lois.
I could listen to
you talk all night.
Yeah, but we got to get going.
Carter's our babysitter,
and if he's with the kids too
long, they start sayin' racisms.
Aw, I wish the fun didn't have
to end.
I always enjoy spending time
with you two.
Well, why don't you
come over tomorrow?
We'll fire up the grill and have
the gang over for a cookout.
Well, that sounds wonderful.
Well, great, we'll be there!
Hey, before you two
leave, let's take a photo.
Yeah! Selfie!
I just learned that word.
Perfect! Well, good
night, you guys.
See you tomorrow,
hashtags!
You're not doin'
that right.
Boy, that Lois is really
something, isn't she?
Yeah. Peter's
a lucky guy.
Glenn, do you...
do you have feelings for her?
- What?
- No.
A mother always knows.
You like to play the
field, but, deep down,
you really wish you had a
woman like Lois, don't you?
No, I don't want a woman
like Lois.
I want Lois.
She's perfect.
I've loved her for years.
She's warm and kind
and beautiful.
I've never been so in love
with anyone.
Glenn, that's
very sweet,
but you're talking about
your best friend's wife.
I know, I know.
It's wrong.
And Peter's
a good friend.
Not like Cleveland.
Hey, I got two
of these phone books.
Didn't know
if you wanted one.
Hey, how long
have we known each other?
Long time. And yet we've never
discussed mothers' maiden names,
the names of old pets,
high school mascots,
favorite teachers.
Heck, I don't even know
the last four digits
of your Social.
Cleveland, do you need
to borrow some money?
I do!
They're gonna kill Donna!
Really?
No. I just want
to buy a man's fur coat.
Get out of here.
Hey, Peter,
I had an extra
phone book, and I...
I'm not buyin' you that coat!
Huh? Who? What?
Yeah, what? What? Which
doggy in what window?
So, how'd everything go?
Hard to tell. I was
coughing the whole time.
By the way, I couldn't figure
out how to use your oven,
so I destroyed it
in a blind rage.
Well, good night.
Ooh, after that steak, I got
to go lay down on the toilet.
Huh. Looks like I got
a couple of messages.
Uh, Dad? Dad?
Grandpa's going nuts
on the oven.
Can you come home quick?
Who the hell is that?
Huh. There's one from Quagmire.
Huh, must've pocket-dialed me
again.
I want Lois. She's perfect.
I've loved her for years.
She's warm and kind
and beautiful.
I've never been so in love
with anyone.
Oh, my God.
Quagmire's in love with my wife?
Hello?
Peter, I'm having troubles
on the toilet.
Bring the ice cream maker.
Brian, there's somethin' I
got to talk to you about.
Quagmire pocket-dialed
me last night.
You got to hear this.
I want Lois. She's perfect.
I've loved her for years.
Oh, my God!
He's in love
with Lois?
Yeah, and if you keep
listenin', you can hear
a Puerto Rican busboy get
fired in the background.
It's pretty funny. He cries.
But can you believe Quagmire?!
Well, I guess
it's not that shocking.
I mean, he has said 100 times
that he wants to bang Lois.
No, no, no, that's just
Quagmire bein' a horndog.
This is love.
I don't know, I think you're making
too big a deal out of this.
Too big a deal?! The guy's
been sitting next to me
all these years,
acting like he's my friend,
when all he really wants
is to be with my wife!
Geez, calm down.
No, I'm telling you,
he's gonna try to take
Lois away from me.
You know what? I'm going
over there right now
and hit him with a shovel, like
a white trash YouTube girl.
Peter, wait, wait.
Listen.
Delete that message
and pretend you never heard it.
What? Why?
Because you weren't meant
to hear it.
If you act on this, all you'll
do is wreck your friendship
and cause heartache
for everyone involved.
What, so what am I supposed
to do, just ignore it?
Yeah. Ignore it.
Like you do with the ghost
of that colonial woman who
died falling down our stairs.
I saw you
eat a crayon...
It was purple.
I thought it was grape.
Look, you've got to be
the bigger man.
You got to just keep this
to yourself.
Fine,
I won't say anything.
Good. And don't be
passive-aggressive, either.
Like one of those songs
in an old musical.
♪ You're hideous ♪
♪ To be without ♪
♪ You're big and fat ♪
♪ In the heart,
no doubt ♪
♪ You're a horrible loss ♪
♪ If you won't be my wife ♪
♪ You're a raging,
continuous ♪
♪ Love in my life... ♪
Pretty good turnout
for this thing.
Oh, yeah, Mort
and Neil Goldman.
It's like Coachella.
There's that son of a bitch!
He's got some nerve
showing up here.
Peter, remember what
we talked about.
Look at them clouds
up there.
Yeah, that one
look like Nathan.
That one look
like Shawn.
And there go Wanya
over there.
How blessed are we to have
all them Boyz II Men
just floating around
in the sky?
Glenn! Ida!
You made it!
Hey, Lois. I brought
the hamburger buns,
like you wanted.
I wasn't sure
what people like,
so I got some with seeds on them
and some without.
What does he mean
by that, "seeds"?
Like semen?
Is that what he means?
Semen on her buns.
Am I the only one hearing this?
Get the hell away from my wife,
you scumbag!
Peter, what are you
talking about?
I'll tell you
what I'm talking about!
I'm talking about this!
Idea for a movie.
Fop Cop. It's a cop
who's, like, a fancy guy.
Nobody heard that!
None of you take that!
What I meant to play was this.
I want Lois. She's perfect.
I've loved her for years.
Fop Cop.
That could work.
Glenn...
i-is this true?
Wait a minute, how the hell'd you get
that recording, Peter?
You pocket-dialed me,
you bastard!
Peter, that was a
private conversation.
That doesn't change the fact
that you want to steal my wife!
Hey, get your
hands off me!
Oh, my God!
- Oh, come on, you two.
- Come on, man.
Hey, what are y'all doing?
Someone stop him!
Kill him, Dad!
Murder him!
That's it!
End of cookout!
Get out of my house, and don't
ever speak to me again!
Wow, that turned ugly fast.
Just like my trip to Tampa Bay.
Hey, city boy,
what's with the arm pants?
I want Lois. She's perfect.
I've loved her for years.
You're still
listening to that thing?
It's like, I can't even process
why he'd feel this way.
Maybe... you know, maybe
play it one more time and...
I can't believe this.
I thought Quagmire
was my friend!
Peter, it's not
that surprising.
He's always had a
potent sex drive.
Remember his
grandmother's funeral?
Yeah, get it in there.
Oh, I wish this was
about sex.
If he was just home
busting one to his buddy's wife,
hell, we've all done that.
I've heard. Allegedly.
But not often.
And never to Donna.
Except when she wore those shiny
gold shorts to parent-teacher night.
Oh, yeah, that
was hilarious.
Yeah, that was...
that was so tacky.
But Quagmire actually has
feelings for you.
I'm afraid he might take you
away from me.
Peter, nobody's
taking me anywhere.
I love you.
Mmm.
I love you, too, Lois.
Hey, you ever heard
any of the other wives
saying they're
attracted to me?
No, um, not that
I recall, no.
Look, now that
this is settled,
maybe you and Glenn can
put this behind you.
No way! How am I supposed
to be friends with someone
who's in love with my wife?
Quagmire is dead to me
and needs to be dealt with
in an appropriate manner.
Shame.
♪ Shame, shame, shame ♪
♪ Shame on you-hoo ♪
♪ Shame on Q... ♪
This was serious, but it
turned into something fun.
Glenn? Is that you?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I was just buying a...
a... grocery store cane.
See you, Lois.
Glenn, wait.
Look, if you and Peter
aren't gonna talk this out,
you and I should.
What's there
to talk about?
Everyone knows I'm in love
with my best friend's wife.
It's pathetic.
And humiliating.
Glenn...
I can't trust myself around you.
It's probably best if I...
just never see you again.
Well, you can't just
avoid me forever.
We live on the same street.
Mm.
Well, then...
I know what I have to do.
Good-bye, Lois.
♪ ♪
Oh, sour cream.
You wanted me to remind you.
Sour cream.
Mr. Quagmire, which box
do these beads go in?
Let me smell 'em.
They go in the big box.
Quagmire, I can't
believe you're moving.
Look, give it time--
this whole thing will blow over.
No, it's too awkward.
It's best for everyone
if I just leave.
That's too bad.
We never got to do
that "Joe-Quagmire" lunch.
Well, that'll do it.
Peter, Quagmire's
serious about this.
You got to do something!
You're right.
Quagmire, wait!
You almost left
without this!
You want me to be the one
that says "jiggety" now?
We now return to Dateline.
Our story tonight:
The guy you think did it?
He did it.
Now go to bed.
Your grandkids
are coming tomorrow.
I had a pretty good
egg dish last night.
What? What-what am I supposed
to do with that information?
Well, I don't know.
Maybe ask me for the recipe?
Do you have it?
No.
So what's going on
with you guys?
Nothing much.
See, this is where Quagmire
normally would have told
one of his
outrageous sex stories.
Aw, we don't need him.
I got a sex story for you.
So I'm bangin' this chick,
and she's sayin' to me,
"I'm worried that Chris won't
get into college."
And then I says to her,
"Yeah, that seems
like a legitimate concern."
And then I lost my wood,
and so we just watched Colbert,
and then I took a dump
completely nude.
Who else but Peter?
Peter, face it-- without
Quagmire, we're boring.
Oh, come on,
that ain't true.
Yes, it is. He had
all the fun ideas.
Remember? He even
took me parasailing.
This is awesome!
It's like I'm flying!
I've never felt so alive!
Oh, if only
I had a pair of legs.
All right!
It was the fish part of me
that wanted 'em!
Look, Peter, I'm
sorry Quagmire moved away,
but you can't just sit around
the house and drink all day.
It's all your fault
Quagmire fell in love with you.
Traipsin' around
in your tan pants
and your green shirt
and your soothing voice.
My fault?!
Yeah, everything is messed up.
I lost my best friend,
my buddies are all fighting,
that chick at work is saying
stuff that ain't true.
Okay, you know what?
Enough feeling
sorry for yourself.
We're fixing this now.
Get in the car.
What? Why?
You'll see.
Why should I trust you?
You're always trickin' me into
going places I don't want to.
Oh... you said we were going
to a place Walt Disney built.
No, Peter. I said supported.
By the way,
don't go on the train ride.
I've been playing
a game I invented
called "mini racquetball"
in your garage.
Uh-huh.
It's pretty fun.
He has not won
a single point.
You don't have to win
to have fun.
Lois? Peter. Zod.
Hey. You're parked behind
my trapezoid-thing.
Yeah, yeah,
I'll move it in a sec.
Glenn, all this nonsense
has to stop now.
The only reason
this became an issue is because
Peter heard something
he wasn't supposed to hear.
Guy from Superman
lives here?!
And the truth is,
we all have private thoughts
we don't act on,
and that's okay.
For instance, every time
I'm on the subway,
I want to push a stranger
onto the tracks.
And that's fine!
I don't do it!
I guess you're right.
I don't totally disagree with
what Kim Jong-un's doing,
but you don't see
me moving there.
I take medicine
I get from the veterinarian.
Is that one?
No, no, it's not,
but the point is,
we all have secret thoughts.
But there's no reason they
should ruin our friendships.
Sometimes I think about
going to the hospital
and switching
the babies around.
Somali pirates
seem cool, too.
I wouldn't mind eating
the Phillie Phanatic.
See? We're all
terrible people inside.
Joe's a little worse
than the rest of us,
but we all just shove
our thoughts deep down,
where they can't
hurt anybody.
Huh, maybe you're right.
Of course I'm right.
The secret to happiness is
burying all your true feelings
and living a life
of bland compromise.
So here's the question, Glenn.
Do you love Peter enough
to repress your love for me?
Peter, if you're willing
to forget all about this,
I'm more than happy to continue
hiding my true feelings.
I do miss us
hanging out together.
Huh. Sorry I kind of
went a little crazy.
Ah, that's all right.
And I'm sorry
I will always love your wife.
Which I don't.
Thank you, Glenn.
All right!
What do you say
we all celebrate
with a game
of mini racquetball?
Wait. Is mini racquetball
just Ping-Pong?
Kind of.
Boy, it's good to have the gang
together again.
Yeah, welcome
home, buddy.
Man, I missed sitting around,
just shooting the breeze.
Hey, so how'd you get
your house back?
This ought to be good.
I suspended escrow.
Oh.
Hey, guys, you know that egg
dish I was talking about?
Turns out that was
just a dream I had.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru